[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 2, "question": "What do you think of Donald Trump banging on about this every day at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "Donald", "Trump", "banging", "on", "about", "this", "every", "day", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 3, "answer": "Well, I think it's a shame.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "shame", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Donald Trump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "He is, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "is", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Yes, he is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Can you still do that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "still", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "I can.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Michelle"]}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "TO", "NNP", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Yes, well, he's made it so family is very important to him and to Michelle and --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "well", ",", "he", "'s", "made", "it", "so", "family", "is", "very", "important", "to", "him", "and", "to", "Michelle", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "The one that no one's allowed to touch?", "question_tokens": ["The", "one", "that", "no", "one", "'s", "allowed", "to", "touch", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 57, "question": "Is that what you can't do anymore?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "ca", "n't", "do", "anymore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Yes, I think --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "I think it's unfortunate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "unfortunate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "What do you think of Donald Trump banging on about this every day at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "Donald", "Trump", "banging", "on", "about", "this", "every", "day", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, I think it's a shame.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "shame", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Donald Trump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "What's he always been like to you as a brother?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "he", "always", "been", "like", "to", "you", "as", "a", "brother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Very big brotherly.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "big", "brotherly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Did he?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Did you listen to him or not?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "listen", "to", "him", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "You know, I did, eventually.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "did", ",", "eventually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Scrabble"]}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Go on, you could do better here?", "question_tokens": ["Go", "on", ",", "you", "could", "do", "better", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Well, I would say that he needs to be more cheerful when he loses to me in Scrabble.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "say", "that", "he", "needs", "to", "be", "more", "cheerful", "when", "he", "loses", "to", "me", "in", "Scrabble", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "What was it like when he actually got in?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "when", "he", "actually", "got", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, I wept profusely as you might imagine, but I also -- our grandmother had just passed away.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "wept", "profusely", "as", "you", "might", "imagine", ",", "but", "I", "also", "--", "our", "grandmother", "had", "just", "passed", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "RB", "NNS", ",", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "What would she have made, do you think, of him as president?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "she", "have", "made", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "of", "him", "as", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Both of our, you know, our motherly elders, both our mom and our grandma would have been tremendously proud.", "answer_tokens": ["Both", "of", "our", ",", "you", "know", ",", "our", "motherly", "elders", ",", "both", "our", "mom", "and", "our", "grandma", "would", "have", "been", "tremendously", "proud", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Is anybody prepared?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "anybody", "prepared", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "I don't think anybody can be fully prepared.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "anybody", "can", "be", "fully", "prepared", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "Would you be happy as a sister to see him run again?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "be", "happy", "as", "a", "sister", "to", "see", "him", "run", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "OETORO-NG: That's -- you know, that's an interesting question.", "answer_tokens": ["OETORO-NG", ":", "That", "'s", "--", "you", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "an", "interesting", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "But when it gets very personal, do you feel that anger boiling up as his sister?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "it", "gets", "very", "personal", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "that", "anger", "boiling", "up", "as", "his", "sister", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "He knew that there would be things that might upset me and he reminded me before he elected to run for president not to get too riled up and not to take it too personally.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "knew", "that", "there", "would", "be", "things", "that", "might", "upset", "me", "and", "he", "reminded", "me", "before", "he", "elected", "to", "run", "for", "president", "not", "to", "get", "too", "riled", "up", "and", "not", "to", "take", "it", "too", "personally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 212, "question": "When you get together for Christmas, I mean who does the cooking and stuff?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "get", "together", "for", "Christmas", ",", "I", "mean", "who", "does", "the", "cooking", "and", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "You know --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "It's not a bad excuse, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "a", "bad", "excuse", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "It's not a bad excuse.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "a", "bad", "excuse", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "What is the message you'd like your daughters to take from this book, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "message", "you", "'d", "like", "your", "daughters", "to", "take", "from", "this", "book", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "There are sort of three messages.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "sort", "of", "three", "messages", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Are you hoping to outdo him with this one?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "hoping", "to", "outdo", "him", "with", "this", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "I can't possibly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "possibly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Fighting the good fight?", "question_tokens": ["Fighting", "the", "good", "fight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "I hope -- you know, I hope so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "hope", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "You're ready to go?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "ready", "to", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "But I'm ready to go.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "I", "'m", "ready", "to", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Is he going to win?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "going", "to", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "You like to win, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "like", "to", "win", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "I -- he needs to win.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "he", "needs", "to", "win", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Or is it just a relentless challenge?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", "just", "a", "relentless", "challenge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "I think he -- I think he really does enjoy seeing a problem and being able to fix it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "--", "I", "think", "he", "really", "does", "enjoy", "seeing", "a", "problem", "and", "being", "able", "to", "fix", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "This would seem to suggest that the economy, which was the central plank of that argument, is in a right old mess, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "would", "seem", "to", "suggest", "that", "the", "economy", ",", "which", "was", "the", "central", "plank", "of", "that", "argument", ",", "is", "in", "a", "right", "old", "mess", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Well, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last year"], "MONEY": ["$2 trillion", "$3.7 trillion"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "DT", "RB", "IN", "$", "CD", "CD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "What percentage of the problem that America now finds itself in economically is down to the Republican administration of the previous eight years, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "percentage", "of", "the", "problem", "that", "America", "now", "finds", "itself", "in", "economically", "is", "down", "to", "the", "Republican", "administration", "of", "the", "previous", "eight", "years", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Well, last year, Piers, they took in at the federal government level a little over $2 trillion in revenue and they spent $3.7 trillion.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "last", "year", ",", "Piers", ",", "they", "took", "in", "at", "the", "federal", "government", "level", "a", "little", "over", "$", "2", "trillion", "in", "revenue", "and", "they", "spent", "$", "3.7", "trillion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, first of all, when he was a United States senator and he faced this issue as a sitting senator, he said that raising the debt ceiling was a sign of flawed leadership.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "when", "he", "was", "a", "United", "States", "senator", "and", "he", "faced", "this", "issue", "as", "a", "sitting", "senator", ",", "he", "said", "that", "raising", "the", "debt", "ceiling", "was", "a", "sign", "of", "flawed", "leadership", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", ":", "CC", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "What's your view of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "view", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Well, I think there's -- and that sentiment, of course, is very raw and it's very real as I travel across the country.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "--", "and", "that", "sentiment", ",", "of", "course", ",", "is", "very", "raw", "and", "it", "'s", "very", "real", "as", "I", "travel", "across", "the", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Would you like to see an element of those bonuses being plowed back into the general economy?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "see", "an", "element", "of", "those", "bonuses", "being", "plowed", "back", "into", "the", "general", "economy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Well, I don't think it's government's job to micromanage salaries in the private sector nor do I support tax increases, and my record is pretty clear on that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "government", "'s", "job", "to", "micromanage", "salaries", "in", "the", "private", "sector", "nor", "do", "I", "support", "tax", "increases", ",", "and", "my", "record", "is", "pretty", "clear", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "I mean, did you not feel slightly unsavory when that was done?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "did", "you", "not", "feel", "slightly", "unsavory", "when", "that", "was", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Did you ever imagine in your wildest nightmares that you'd see a poll of potential Republican candidates which had you at two percent and Donald Trump at 19 percent?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "in", "your", "wildest", "nightmares", "that", "you", "'d", "see", "a", "poll", "of", "potential", "Republican", "candidates", "which", "had", "you", "at", "two", "percent", "and", "Donald", "Trump", "at", "19", "percent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Well, I'm just -- for me just getting known, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "just", "--", "for", "me", "just", "getting", "known", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump"], "PERCENT": ["19 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Do you think it may come down to the hair, do you, governor?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "may", "come", "down", "to", "the", "hair", ",", "do", "you", ",", "governor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CC", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Yeah, I could have the big flop or the mullet.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "could", "have", "the", "big", "flop", "or", "the", "mullet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse Ventura"]}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Do you sense that happening, that there is this vacuum?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "sense", "that", "happening", ",", "that", "there", "is", "this", "vacuum", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "You're talking to somebody who is the governor of the state that elected Jesse Ventura as governor and Al Franken as senator.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "talking", "to", "somebody", "who", "is", "the", "governor", "of", "the", "state", "that", "elected", "Jesse", "Ventura", "as", "governor", "and", "Al", "Franken", "as", "senator", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Do you believe that President Obama was born in Hawaii?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "President", "Obama", "was", "born", "in", "Hawaii", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "I do, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Hawaii"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "In a hypothetical scenario, governor, if someone like Donald Trump was to emerge as the Republican nominee, and asked you to be vice president, would you accept that honor?", "question_tokens": ["In", "a", "hypothetical", "scenario", ",", "governor", ",", "if", "someone", "like", "Donald", "Trump", "was", "to", "emerge", "as", "the", "Republican", "nominee", ",", "and", "asked", "you", "to", "be", "vice", "president", ",", "would", "you", "accept", "that", "honor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "I'm running for president.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "running", "for", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Can we take that as an official announcement?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "take", "that", "as", "an", "official", "announcement", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Well, I have an exploratory committee up and running.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "an", "exploratory", "committee", "up", "and", "running", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Is that fair?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "fair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Well, I think, Piers, they've been working hard to deal with a very difficult situation.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", ",", "Piers", ",", "they", "'ve", "been", "working", "hard", "to", "deal", "with", "a", "very", "difficult", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Not just in Japan, but perhaps to America and to the wider world?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "just", "in", "Japan", ",", "but", "perhaps", "to", "America", "and", "to", "the", "wider", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Well, I want to be clear, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "want", "to", "be", "clear", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Do you see fundamental changes as a result of what we've seen in Japan?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "see", "fundamental", "changes", "as", "a", "result", "of", "what", "we", "'ve", "seen", "in", "Japan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Well, we have really a two-pronged approach that we're going to use to take a look at that very question.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "have", "really", "a", "two-pronged", "approach", "that", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "use", "to", "take", "a", "look", "at", "that", "very", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Tokyo", "Japan"]}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "But should we be getting quite critical now of the level of information coming out of the Japanese authorities?", "question_tokens": ["But", "should", "we", "be", "getting", "quite", "critical", "now", "of", "the", "level", "of", "information", "coming", "out", "of", "the", "Japanese", "authorities", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Well, Piers, we have a team of experts that is in Tokyo, that is interfacing very closely with experts from the Japanese government and experts from the industry and utility in Japan.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "we", "have", "a", "team", "of", "experts", "that", "is", "in", "Tokyo", ",", "that", "is", "interfacing", "very", "closely", "with", "experts", "from", "the", "Japanese", "government", "and", "experts", "from", "the", "industry", "and", "utility", "in", "Japan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States", "Hawaii", "Alaska", "United States"]}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "EX", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Is it 100 percent certain that there is going to be no risk here to Americans, for example, on the coastline here?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "100", "percent", "certain", "that", "there", "is", "going", "to", "be", "no", "risk", "here", "to", "Americans", ",", "for", "example", ",", "on", "the", "coastline", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Yeah, we have strong confidence that there really is no likelihood of any kind of significant impact to the United States or any Hawaii or Alaska or any of the territories of the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "we", "have", "strong", "confidence", "that", "there", "really", "is", "no", "likelihood", "of", "any", "kind", "of", "significant", "impact", "to", "the", "United", "States", "or", "any", "Hawaii", "or", "Alaska", "or", "any", "of", "the", "territories", "of", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "How do you deal with this kind of leak?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "deal", "with", "this", "kind", "of", "leak", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Well, right now, the focus is on making sure that the reactors stay cool and that the spent fuel pools can be put in a safe, stable configuration.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "right", "now", ",", "the", "focus", "is", "on", "making", "sure", "that", "the", "reactors", "stay", "cool", "and", "that", "the", "spent", "fuel", "pools", "can", "be", "put", "in", "a", "safe", ",", "stable", "configuration", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Are you 100 percent satisfied that America is prepared for that kind of eventuality, or even a bigger earthquake and tsunami?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "100", "percent", "satisfied", "that", "America", "is", "prepared", "for", "that", "kind", "of", "eventuality", ",", "or", "even", "a", "bigger", "earthquake", "and", "tsunami", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "We think the plants in this country are safe and they continue to operate safely.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "think", "the", "plants", "in", "this", "country", "are", "safe", "and", "they", "continue", "to", "operate", "safely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Good morning, Katie, I think it is for you, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Good", "morning", ",", "Katie", ",", "I", "think", "it", "is", "for", "you", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Almost.", "answer_tokens": ["Almost", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Katie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sara Boson"]}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Do we have any indication of who's made the wedding dress yet?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "have", "any", "indication", "of", "who", "'s", "made", "the", "wedding", "dress", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Well, the name on everyone's list is still Sara Boson (ph) from the queen.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "name", "on", "everyone", "'s", "list", "is", "still", "Sara", "Boson", "(", "ph", ")", "from", "the", "queen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "What about the guest list for what the going to be the wedding of the millennium?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "the", "guest", "list", "for", "what", "the", "going", "to", "be", "the", "wedding", "of", "the", "millennium", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "The guest list is fascinating.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "guest", "list", "is", "fascinating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "And the world media and the world itself will be watching what I think is going to be a quite extraordinary and hopefully uplifting event, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "world", "media", "and", "the", "world", "itself", "will", "be", "watching", "what", "I", "think", "is", "going", "to", "be", "a", "quite", "extraordinary", "and", "hopefully", "uplifting", "event", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "I think it's going to be fantastic.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "fantastic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]